#PassTheBaton
Drumline: A New Beat is a music, comedy, drama film directed by Bille Woodruff.
A girl from New York attends a college in Atlanta to
join their once-famous marching band.
Dani Bolton, played by Alexandra Shipp.
Dr. Sean Taylor, played by Leonard Roberts.
Jayven LaPierre, played by Jordan Calloway.
Dr. Nia Phillips, played by LeToya Luckett.
Tasha, played by Jasmine Burke.
Lois Bolton, played by Lisa Arrindell.
Drumline: A New Beat is a 2014 American television
film directed by Bille Woodruff.
It is the sequel to 2002's Drumline.
The screenplay, a fictional story about a historically black college
marching band, was written by Karen Gist and Regina Hicks.
The story is about a young drummer from New York, played by Alexandra Shipp, who enters the fictional
Atlanta A&T University and bumps heads with the leader of her new school's drum section.
Jordan Calloway, Mario Van Peebles, and LeToya Luckett co-star.
Leonard Roberts reprises his role as Sean Taylor, while Nick
Cannon was the film's executive producer.
The film premiered on VH1 on October 21, 2014, and
released to DVD on March 3, 2015.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.